var questions = [{
  question:'The downcase method belongs to which language?',
  choices:['Ruby','Javascript','Python','C++'],
  answer: 'Ruby'
},{
  question:'In Javascript how would you turn the word hello into an array of a string? ',
  choices: ['split()','pop()','slice()','push()'],
  answer: 'split()'
},{
  question:"what is DT's favourite color?",
  choices:['black','mistyRose','darkOliveGreen', 'crimson'],
  answer:'mistyRose'
},{
  question:'web pages are bulit using ?',
  choices:['FTP', 'HTTP', 'HTML', 'URL'],
  answer: 'HTML'
},{
  question:'In What year was HTML first Proposed?',
  choices:['1990', '1985','2000', '1995'],
  answer: '1990'
},{
  question:'what should be the first tag in any HTML document?',
  choices:['<head>','<html>','<body>','<title>'],
  answer: '<html>'
}, {
  question:'Which of the following is not a browser ? ',
  choices:['Microsofts Bing','Netscape Navigator','Mozilla Firefox','Opera'],
  answer:'Microsofts Bing'
},{
  question:'Which type of error is caused when code is executed but there are undesired results?',
  choices:['Runtime error','Browser error','Syntax error','Logic error'],
  answer:'Logic error'
},{
  question: 'which of these Math. methods returns the value rounded up to the nearest integer?',
  choices:['Math.floor()','Math.random()','Math.ceil()','Math.round()'],
  answer:'Math.ceil()'
},{
  question:'which of these is not a reserved word in Javascript?',
  choices: ['debugger','null','break',
'broke'],
  answer: 'broke'
},{
  question:'pick the html tag that uses .value instead of .textContent when getting the text in the DOM?',
  choices:['<input>','<h1>','<p>','<form>'],
  answer:'<input>'
},{
  question:'which of these is not a click event?',
  choices:['onmouseover','onmouseout','onclick','onmouseleft'],
  answer:'onmouseleft'
},{
  question:'in CSS which of these dont belong to the display property?',
  choices:['block','grid','inline','list'],
  answer:'list'
},{
  question:'which of these is not a way to collect an item from the DOM?',
  choices: ['getElementById','getElementsById','getElementsByTagName','getElementsByClassName'],
  answer:'getElementsById'
},{
  question:'which of these characters are not allowed to be used to start a variable name in Javascript',
  choices:['_','$','1','#'],
  answer:'#'
},{
  question:'nearly everything in Ruby is condsidered a what?',
  choices:['variable','object','function','proc'],
  answer:'object'
},{
  question:'because Ruby is an interpreted language, it means that a source code complied and executed at what?',
  choices:['Runtime','After Lunch','Before','later'],
  answer:'Runtime'
}, {
  question:'which of these is not a primitive?',
  choices: ['string','number','array','boolean'],
  answer: 'array'
}, {
  question:'which of of these is not a correct syntax in Javascript?',
  choices: ['==','>=','<=','=<'],
  answer: '=<'
}, {
  question:'which od these is not classed as a scope in Ruby',
  choices: ['global','class','local','instant'],
  answer: 'instant'
}, {
  question:'which of theses has the incorrect Syntax?',
  choices: ['createElement()','createTextsNode()','appendChild()','removeChild()'],
  answer: 'createTextsNode()'
}, {
  question:'which is not a loop in Javascript?',
  choices: ['for','each','while','do while'],
  answer: 'each'
}, {
  question:'which of these is not a basic box property in CSS',
  choices: ['left','top','up','float'],
  answer: 'up'
}, {
  question:'To specifies a fonts boldness in CSS you use Font-what?',
  choices: ['bold','weight','style','family'],
  answer: 'weight'
}, {
  question:'which of these is not a valid cursor property?',
  choices: ['not-allowed','no-drop','crosshair','no-target'],
  answer: 'no-target'
}];
